MkvDrama.net
Previously on Dating Alys Perez.
I've made up my mind.
Let's call it quits.
Try and get in that cab, Drake!
I won't let you back in my life.
Drake!
Are you dating my cousin?
Yes.
What does it have to do with you?
Nothing!
Just checking the competition.
So you're telling me
that Drake's hit on you?
Maybe seeing you again
brought back the old flame.
So, tell me.
How was your first day
and how was your first client?
Okay, I guess.
A little distressing.
I mean...
There were some
challenging requests but
nothing I couldn't
handle, as usual.
Of course.
You've got this.
By the way,
I've got good news for you.
I'll be joining you much sooner.
Oh, my gosh!
Thank you so much, St. Colette!
She probably answered my
prayers to be with you.
You must've prayed a lot.
Yeah!
Being here without you
is driving me insane.
I really need you here, Tripp.
Don't worry.
I'll see you soon, Silly!
See you!
Bye!
Good morning, St. Colette.
I hope we'll be in a
good mood all day.
Good mood, good vibes.
Alys,
Uncle Steve called.
Did he say why?
I don't know.
He just asked you to see him.
Okay.
Thank you, Dane.
Oh my gosh, he called five times.
Hello?
Yes?
Can you give the
phone to Uncle Steve?
Why?
I need to ask why
he wants to see me.
I don't know.
What?
Can you just give him the phone?
I don’t want!
It's Ethos' birthday.
Oh fuck, right.
Since when did
you start cursing?
Since, I don't know
and you don't care.
Can you just tell Uncle Steve
that I'm swinging by later?
Bye.
How could I forget?
The conference is over.
I'll be there the day after tomorrow.
Really?
Oh?
Something wrong?
I don't want to lose
my silly girlfriend.
You're really something,
Tripp Marco Palma.
I almost felt giddy.
I'm kidding, come on.
I really miss you, silly.
If you did, you'd be here already.
You know,
you won't find another pretty girl
you can trick in New York.
This is what I like about him.
We can just talk and
have a good laugh.
Sometimes,
people don't want a
complicated relationship.
In my case, I like things like this.
Simple, comfortable,
no chaos.
Just pure rainbow
and butterflies.
No stormy days.
Hey!
I can be attractive, you know.
Okay.
Whatever you say.
Anyways...
See you soon!
Alright.
See you, silly.
I love you.
I love you, too.
What are you thinking about?
Nothing.
Alys.
What else do I have to do,
so you'll believe me
when I say it's only you?
Hmm?
My name is Alys.
Alys Zyril Perez.
Soon to be Palma!
Bird brain.
So annoying.
You'll be my noob.
Mine, and mine only.
[In French] Only you.
Alys!
Welcome back!
Uncle Steve!
Hi, I missed you!
Glad you made it!
Of course, Uncle.
Oh!
My gift for Ethos.
Where is my godchild?
He's with Drake.
They’re in the pavilion.
Why don't you give
it to him yourself?
Oh, then I will.
See you around, Uncle.
Baby Ethos!
- Baby Ethos!
- Stop your baby talk.
You're annoying him.
No, I'm not!
I'm cute and you know it!
Isn't that right, Baby Ethos?
Right?
Drake is such a meanie, oh my gosh.
Whoa!
Aren't we a little early, Perez?
Here.
Your order.
Wow!
You like it?
Oh!
Jen!
Did we get our supply of sodas?
Yes, sir.
In fairness, Tofer,
the restobar looks great.
You know it makes me wonder...
Why go through all that trouble
taking Advertising in New York
just to go into the Food Industry...
Too many questions!
Just taste the thing, alright?
Melanie!
Check on table number five.
Take their order.
- Yes, sir.
- Go.
It's great!
Approved!
Five stars?
Oh, where's Cai?
Cai?
Check on table number two.
They're asking for water.
Tofer?
Hmm?
Why are all your
employees women?
It's Dad.
He told me
that if he saw a man working here
he'd disown me.
Did he really say that?
Yes, he did.
But Alys, in all seriousness...
Look at me.
Look at me right now.
Do I really look gay to you?
Wait.
Wait a sec, Tofer.
Do you really want an honest answer?
Mmm...
You're a little short on masculinity.
You'll live.
Come on, Alys.
Aww, Baby Tofer...
Stop that!
Just because
I dress the way I do and
and wear lip balm.
I’m automatically gay?
You're all judgemental!
Tofer...
He's cute.
Is he your type?
I am not gay!
No crepe!
Hey, that's my crepe!
I paid for that! Tofer!
I'm gonna have this place blacklisted!
Tofer!
Oh no, you didn't!
Don't be dramatic!
I was just kidding...
Hey, don't we always
joke around like this?
Seriously, Tofer. What's wrong?
This is nothing.
It's just hard being
Drake and Tripp's cousin.
Their expectations
are through the roof.
You don't know, Alys.
When we were kids,
they were already competing.
Even before that,
it started way back
between their families.
With Uncle Tristan
and Uncle Steve.
And so,
it hasn't stopped since.
And you know Drake.
Gifted.
Smart.
Genius.
As for Tripp,
you know him too.
His IQ's above average too.
And then there's Tofer.
I guess that's it.
I felt left behind.
And now,
Drake has been ignoring me.
So?
Didn't you say Tripp
was your favorite cousin?
Of course.
But the thing is, Alys...
Never mind.
It's better not to tell you.
It’s okay if you don’t want to tell me.
But I just want you to know
that I'm always here for you.
Okay?
Don't ever be afraid to tell me.
You're basically my little brother.
Come on, cheer up!
Are you okay?
Are you sure?
Just give me a call whenever.
I really have to go.
I'm sorry.
Bye, Tofer.
Hi, Charmaine!
Where's mommy?
Oh, you missed her.
She had somewhere to go.
Okay.
Wow.
She really looks great.
No wonder Drake will marry her.
She looks awesome and
she's good with kids.
Just as she was when
I saw them together.
They really look like a family.
It’s kinda loose here.
Sure, we’ll tighten it for you.
Thank you.
Oh.
You're here.
Is it really just me or
does she really not like me?
It's nice to see you, Ms. Stinson.
Good to see you as well.
When I saw him with Drake,
she seemed so bubbly and stuff.
But now that we're alone,
she has this aura of a
stiff and a snob.
Does she hate me?
By the way, Ms. Stinson, how're
the wedding preparations going?
Kind of stressful
but it's pushing through.
Good thing Drake's really
hands-on with all this stuff.
Yeah, good thing Mr. Palma's
very hands-on.
Well, yes.
You know, even though he
has a lot on his plate,
he still finds time to help me
with all these arrangements.
One in a million, that he is.
Good thing I found him.
If you don't mind me asking, Ms. Stinson,
how did you two meet?
Okay. So, during college,
we became orgmates.
Actually, we didn't really talk at first.
But,
we had a common friend so
we'd see each other at events.
And then we instantly clicked,
and then we became BFFs.
Actually, I became
close with his family, too.
Especially, Baby Ethos.
Well, I became Ethos' playmate
because they always had me over.
Nanny, can I have my water, please?
Okay, so going back...
Because we were always together,
well...
We developed feelings
for each other.
He courted me.
And I said, yes.
Two years ago.
September 13.
September 13?
Yes.
Why?
Oh, nothing.
Same as my anniversary with Tripp.
What a coincidence.
What coincidence?
Oh, it's nothing.
Don't mind me,
I love talking to myself.
What's with her that Drake
dropped on his knee?
What was I missing that
Drake would leave me?
Oh, by the way...
Have you been to Drake's office?
It's in the DCL Building in Ortigas.
Nope.
Not really.
Okay.
So going back...
I think Drake and I are
really meant for one another.
Don't you think so too, Alys?
Huh?
Yeah, actually
you two would make a great couple.
Oh, we'll surely do, Ms. Perez.
We'll surely do.
By the way,
are you done with the train?
Yes, Ma'am.
Oh, can I see it?
Just a moment, Alys.
Oh my god! That's so pretty.
Damn it, Alys!
You already have Tripp.
Why are you comparing yourself to her?
Thank you so much for coming!
We hope you liked the food!
Post on social media
if you can, okay?
Thank you so much!
Alys, congrats! Congrats!
Thank you!
Thank you for coming!
- Aya, my loves!
- Bestie!
I missed you!
- Wow, your outfit looks amazing!
- Of course!
I love it!
Oh, hang on, Bestie!
Got something I need to do.
It's fine, go go!
Classmates! Oh my god!
What do you guys do now?
Thank you!
Alys!
- Mommy!
- Congratulations!
Congratulations, dear.
Hey, Dad!
Thank you for coming.
Congratulations!
- Hi, Baby Dane!
- Alys!
- Oh! You're so cute!
Go to the cupcake tower, hurry!
Go!
That's a bit too "mom" of you, Mommy.
Of course, I want to capture
this moment, Baby Dear.
Oh!
Here.
Hey, get your hands off my cake!
Give it to me.
It's mine.
I'm taking it home.
No, it's mine.
Go make a new one!
I said no!
This is mine!
It's mine now.
I said it's mine!
My cake!
Alys!
Smile!
Different pose!
I'm sorry, Mom.
I have to answer this.
Alright.
I'll be right back.
Hey, silly!
Hi, my silly!
How's the store opening?
Everything went well.
You're the only thing missing.
I know, but we'll be together soon.
Just a little patience.
I love you, silly.
I love you, too.
Excuse me.
Yes, Ma'am?
Where is Tofer?
He’s in his office, Ma'am.
Thank you.
Tofer?
Hey!
Congrats on the opening, Perez!
Sorry I couldn't make it.
Why am I not surprised?
I sent flowers!
Here.
For you.
Hey!
You really shouldn't have!
Thank you.
I can finally try.
"Cupcakes by Alys".
So...
What brings you here?
How can I be of service, Ms. Perez?
Well, I'm going over to Uncle Steve's.
What for?
Godmother duties.
I promised I'd go see Ethos
for some bonding time.
So, wait.
You came all this way
just to tell me that?
You're weird.
No.
I just
need to know if
Drake will be there later.
Why?
Don't tell me...
Don't be an idiot!
Oh, Tripp's going to be mad.
I’m going to call him!
Stop it!
I just want to know if he'll be there
so I can avoid him.
I really don't want
to see that face of his.
It'd ruin my day.
And I also know that you're
basically made of gossip.
You knew things before Nostrodamus did.
Of course!
It's called thinking ahead.
So?
Drake will be there around 9:00 PM.
You should be safe.
Stop worrying.
Okay!
Thanks, Tofer!
Bye!
And that's how she is when
she gets what she wants.
What?
You want to tag along?
Just go! I'm busy.
Bye!
Aunt Katrina!
Oh, Alys!
Hi!
Hello, Auntie.
Ethos!
Is that the toy train
that I gave you?
Here's another gift!
Baby Ethos!
What brings you here, Alys?
Do you need something?
No, Auntie.
Just here to give a gift for Ethos.
He's so cute, Auntie.
He looks just like Uncle Steve!
People always say that.
Nobody ever said
that he looks like me.
Lady...
Would you kindly prepare
snacks for our guest?
Oh, no Auntie.
There's no need!
I'm fine, you don't have to.
It's fine. It's not everyday
we get to see you.
Did Drake invite you
to the wedding?
What?
Alys,
I know it's not my place to say this.
But Drake waited for you.
He waited, Alys.
But now, he's happy with Cristine.
So I’m asking you not to make trouble.
Wait, what?
Now I'm making trouble?
You confuse him, Alys.
You always do.
Alys!
Uncle Steve!
Hi!
What brings you here?
Oh, I just came by to
drop off Ethos' gift.
He's so cute, Uncle!
He looks just like you!
You're just as bad as Drake.
You keep spoiling Ethos.
How can I resist when
he's just so cute?
That's right.
He waited, Alys.
But now, he's happy with Cristine.
So, I'm asking you to not make trouble.
Alys.
We never got a chance
to talk at Ethos' party.
I know, Uncle.
It was really crowded.
I'm glad you dropped by.
Ethos is such a smart kid.
His mom and I started him at kindergarten.
And he's got his mother's full attention.
Oh no, I think you have
another little genius, Uncle.
That's true.
He could be as smart
as his big brother.
I just hope he'll be nicer.
I hope so, too.
Uhm...
Uncle?
How is Drake?
I was hoping you'd ask that.
He's doing okay.
He's happy with Cristine.
And it's great that
she makes Drake happy.
Good!
I'm glad to know that, Uncle.
Alys,
don't get me wrong.
I've always wanted you for Drake.
But Cristine,
I'm fine with her.
As long as Drake is happy.
And I know she'll never leave Drake.
Uncle,
we're over.
If he's happy, I'm happy.
That's great, Alys.
Drake and Cristine
became bestfriends
when you two broke up.
After we broke up?
Yes.
They were classmates,
and she always came over,
they became close.
Cristine was the only one who
could get him out of his shell.
That's why I liked her.
Am I not a good influence for Drake?
I never taught him to do anything bad.
I wasn't doing great at academics but,
that doesn't mean I'm a bad influence.
Alys, you okay?
I'm fine, Uncle.
Uncle?
I just wanted to ask
when did they get together?
Honestly, I don't know.
I just found out that
they were getting married.
And I was't going to complain because
they're great for each other.
What about you, Alys?
How are you?
I haven't seen you in four years!
Steve, Alys?
Let's eat?
Alys, let's eat?
Sure, Uncle.
Okay, excuse me for a bit.
Baby Ethos?
Ate Alys is going now.
Bye, Bye, Ethos.
Bye, Alys.
Baby Ethos?
Can you call Ate Alys, "Ate"?
Please?
No, I don't want to.
Why not, Ethos?
Alys is not nice.
You make Drake cry.
Alys is bad.
What the hell, Drake?
You hurt me back then.
How am I the villain now?
Ethos?
Ate Alys is not bad.
Okay?
Ate Alys, will tell you.
Ate Alys will explain to you. Okay?
I don't want Alys here.
You make Drake cry again.
Alys is bad.
I don't want Alys here.
You make Drake cry.
Alys is bad!
Get out!
Oh! Excuse me.
Another round of cosmos please.
Thank you!
Why am I so bothered by a four year-old?
Nobody can control how a child thinks.
Hey!
What's eating you, this time?
Chill, Perez!
- I am chill!
- Are you drunk?
What?!
Are you drunk?!
I'm not drunk!
Here we go again.
I'm not deaf either!
Whoa.
You've even got Cosmos!
Looks like you've been through a lot.
We had our hands full at the bar.
Why did you call for an S.O.S?
I needed somebody to drive me home!
So now I'm your driver!
You're unbelievable, Perez.
Tofer, we've been through this.
It's just like when
we were in Paris.
You were my guardian angel
while Tripp was in New York.
Oh, yeah, Paris.
You were like...
Okay, fine.
So?
Is it time for bitch mode again?
Zyril?
Am I back?
Tofer...
Meet my doppelganger.
Zyril.
Here we go again.
Zyril!
Zyril is my name!
Hi, my name is Zyril!
Coming through!
My name is Zyril!
Zyril!
Wow, you have such a badass name!
I know, right?!
Are you new here?
Yeah, actually I just transferred here
from New York to study culinary.
New York was a fucking mess!
It was a hot mess!
Good for you!
Are you having fun so far?
Isn't it obvious?
Let's party!
- My name is Zyril!
- Alys!
Tofer, it's you!
Come on, let's party.
Let's dance!
Alys, you're drunk.
Let's go home!
I'm not drunk!
Let's dance!
Alys!
Don’t be such a killjoy!
Let's party!
Alys, you've been drinking all night!
Pull yourself together, Alys!
Come on, let's go home, please!
Alys!
I don't get it.
Why won't the pain go away?
Alys...
You're funny.
- Please stop.
- I can’t do it anymore...
Stop, Alys.
Stop.
Stop, Alys!
Alys, enough!
- I said, enough.
- I can't do it anymore!
- Stop it, Alys!
- I can't do this anymore!
- Alys, enough!
Alys!
Wake up, Alys!
Alys, wake up!
Alys!
Dane?
What is it?
What time is it?
It's 7:00 AM. Get up!
7:00 AM?
Why would you wake me up this early?
What do you need from me?
You know, good thing Mom
didn't see you last night.
You look stupid when you're drunk.
Sorry, I went out partying with Tofer.
Whatever, it's done.
You looked weird
when you got home.
Anyway...
Mom said, take care.
We'll be gone for a while.
Huh?
Where are you off to?
We'll go to this resort in Algeria?
Something?
I don't know.
She had me tell you because
they won't be able to come by.
Okay.
Wait...
are you leaving me too, Baby Dane?
Quit it.
You don't need me anyway.
You need Drake.
What do you mean, I need Drake?
I survived four years without him.
What difference does it make
now that he's gone from my life?
And besides,
don't you all get it?
He's getting married!
Whatever you say.
One thing is for sure, though.
You look stupid, Alys.
Alcohol won't fix anything.
And you should know better.
When did you learn to get drunk?
And bite!
Waiter!
[In French] Three more rounds, please!
Again!
Okay, okay!
Oh my god!
One more, one more!
- Yeah!
- Again!
Okay!
Lick.
Shot.
And bite!
Oh my god!
Drink and forget.
Forget Drake, Alys!
Forget Drake!
Drink 'til you forget.
[In French] Only you.
Bird brain.
You'll be my noob.
My noob.
Mine and mine only.
[In French] Only you.
You'll be my noob.
Bird brain.
Mine and mine only.
[In French] Only you.
I wanna dance!
Hey, where are you going?
Unbelievable!
Why are you always like this?
Alys!
Aren't you tired of this?
I thought we came all the way to Paris
so you could change?
- Bleh-bleh-bleh!
- You’re destroying yourself!
Can you not?
Would you stop lecturing me?
Where are my friends anyway?
Oh!
Your French friends?
Those drunks?
Mhm.
They left you.
Do you know what they said?
"Oh this girl is so crazy!
She's such a hypocrite!"
They left me?
They all keep leaving me.
Alys, there you go again!
Would you please stop that?!
Is this still about Drake?
Alys!
You already have Tripp, right?
I can't understand you!
You know what?!
If you really want to ruin your life,
just say so!
Instead of wasting my time here.
Fine, then! Leave!
Stop trying to be a hero.
I'll be fine.
I never asked you to come!
Just go!
Oh, really?!
Really?!
Alright, then!
Fine!
Go home by yourself!
Goodbye!
Just go!
I don't need you!
Leave!
You're worthless anyway!
Oh!
My god!
What is this?
Why?!
Whoa!
You seem pissed.
Honestly, I'm not in the mood to talk.
But Tripp's the only one left.
I can't ignore him.
No, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Tripp.
I'm not feeling well, is all.
Huh?
Why?
Why don't you get a check-up?
No, I'm fine.
I'm just feeling a bit
under the weather.
You know, I'm adjusting to
the weather over here.
What about you?
How are you?
How's life alone?
The same.
You?
Have you adjusted to it?
I want to say that I've
completely adjusted to it.
I've gotten good at going to the bar
and coming home in the morning.
But of course,
I can't tell Tripp about that.
I've caused him enough trouble.
I can't keep doing that.
Hello?
Zy?
Yes?
I'm sorry, uhm...
Yes! I'm okay.
I've adapted to this place, somewhat.
I have to go, Tripp, okay?
I have so many things to do.
Bye, bye.
To be honest,
I don't like talking to Tripp
because of all the
lies I have to tell him.
He deserves better.
And...
I'm not better.
I'm worse.
He doesn't deserve the
end of a schmick stick.
Oh, Alys, when will you be okay?
Wow, I look pretty today!
Who are you again?
Perfect.
Good morning, Sir Drake!
What is it now?
Drake, can you not?!
I just wanted a perfect day!
Don't ruin this for me!
Oh my god, what does he
want now?
Damn it! I forgot to lock it!
Where are we going?
What do you mean
where are we going?
Why are you even here?
Feeling close?
Are we close now?
Alys,
we were pretty close.
We're exes, remember?
We used to hug.
We used to...
What do you want, Drake?!
What do you need?
Why are you even here?!
Alys!
Chill out!
You don't have to be so pissed.
You'll get wrinkles, you know.
And?
Why do you care?
So what if I get wrinkles?
Tripp doesn't like ugly girls.
Anyway,
go drive.
Inhale, exhale.
Calm down, Alys. Calm down.
Are you getting out or not?
Don’t look, Alys.
Don’t look.
You won’t get fooled.
I said don’t look, Alys.
Hello?
Your office?
Okay, got it.
Thanks! See yah, bye!
Who's that?
Are we here?
You are.
Get out!
Wait.
Why are we here, Alys?
Where else?
Isn't this your office?
DCL Building in Ortigas?
Go ahead and meet your fiancée.
And please!
Please, Drake!
Will you leave me the fuck alone?
We’re over, right?
Four years ago.
In front of the hotel where
you were staying at.
Remember me?
Alys Perez?
The girl you freakin’ destroyed?
Look at me now, Drake.
I'm better.
And I'm so fucking happy without you.
It took me years to be finally like this.
And there's no way in hell
I'm letting you pull me back down
to the pit you've created for me.
Get out!
See you tonight, Alys.
Good morning, Sir!
The nerve!
How annoying!
So stressful!
You haven’t changed.
Tripp will be here in two days, Alys.
He can't come back to find this.
I don't want Tripp and I to fight
over that damn Drake Palma.
Okay.
Let's end this madness
once and for all, Drake.
Good morning, Ma'am.
Where's Drake's office?
May I have your name?
I'm Alys Perez. Do you need an ID?
Alys Perez?
Does she know me?
Why is she surprised?
No need for an ID.
Go straight to the hallway, Ma’am.
Turn right,
turn right
and then turn right.
Okay, I go straight then...
Right, right, right?
Yes, Ma'am.
- Alright, thank you.
- Thank you.
Drake Palma’s Office.
Enter your 4-digit code
after 00, then press #.
Should I call Cristine?
No, never mind.
I'm not that close to ask personal stuff.
What was their anniversary again?
Ours are related somehow.
So, September 13th.
Do we really have the same date?
Out of all the days in a year,
the same date?
It's too much of a coincidence, but,
I'll just give it the benefit of the doubt.
0, 0, 0, 9, 1, 3.
Verification failed.
I know this has only three tries.
I have two tries left.
Drake's birthday!
0, 0, 1, 2, 2, 9.
Verification failed.
Think, Alys, think.
No!
Drake wouldn't make that his passcode.
He has a fiancée.
Can’t he move on?
Fine!
Here goes nothing.
0, 0, 1, 1, 3, 1.
Unlocked.
Hey, Palma.
The wedding's coming sooner
than we think.
I really hope everything's
gonna be okay.
Why?
Having second thoughts?
I'm not having second thoughts.
I just want everything
to be perfect for you.
I don't want to ruin
everything we've built.
You were never like this.
You were excited, remember?
I know, it's just...
Please, tell me it'll be worth it.
Promise.
Are you sure?
Alys, won't be a problem?
Okay, I have to go.
I hope I'm still making the right decision.
On the next episode of
Dating Alys Perez.
Silly!
When are you coming here?
Soon.
I'll surprise you.
Silly, you're here!
Drake, what the hell?!
Hey, Silly!
Tripp!
Hey!
Silly!
I said,
anything interesting happened?
Nothing.
I saw Tripp yesterday.
My god, Alys.
I knew he looked good, but...
damn, Tripp has gotten
even more handsome.
I know.
- Right?
- I know, right?
I'm so lucky.
What the hell is your problem, Drake?!
Never do that again!
I can't promise that.
We missed your 20th birthday.
Remember when I told you,
that I'll let you have my
body on that special day.
You freakin’, freakin’ jerk!
MkvDrama.net